Finding Aid for Claude Thomas Stoner Photographs and Papers 1870s-1977
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Classified Photographs
  - Logging Railroads
    - Engine and log train, [LR114] (Box 1)
    - Lake George & Muskegon River (Box 1)
    - Loading log train circa 1880, [LR115] (Box 1)
    - Details of LR115, [LR116-117] (Box 1)
    - Hermansville & Western, Wisconsin Land & Lumber Co., Hermansville, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine Pioneer and log car, [LR118-119] (Box 1)
    - Louis Sands Salt & Lumber Co., Manistee, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine Mattie B. Sands, [LR120] (Box 1)
    - Antrim Iron Co., Mancelona, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, [LR121] (Box 1)
    - Wisconsin Land & Lumber Co., Hermansville, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 5 ready for scrapping, [LR122] (Box 1)
    - Shay engine in park, Cadillac, Mich., [LR123] (Box 1)
    - Historical marker between Clare and Harrison, Mich., [LR124] (Box 1)
    - Cobbs & Mitchell, Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 3, Crofton, Mich., [LR125] (Box 1)
    - Boyne Falls & Northeastern, Cobbs & Mitchell (Box 1)
    - Engine 7, [LR126] (Box 1)
    - Hemlock Central, E. Shay & Son, Harbor Springs, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 2 and log train, [LR127] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3, [LR128] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and log train, [LR129-131] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and log loader, [LR132] (Box 1)
    - Bear Lake & Eastern, Hopkins Manufacturing Co., Bear Lake, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Three engines stored at Manistee, Mich. circa 1915, [LR133] (Box 1)
    - Horning & Hart, Woodville, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Old Shay engine circa 1896, [LR134] (Box 1)
    - Jennings & Northeastern, Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - Engine 7, [LR135] (Box 1)
    - Bridal Veil Lumbering Co., Bridal Veil, Ore. (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, [LR136] (Box 1)
    - Cummer Lumber Co., Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine and log train, [LR137] (Box 1)
    - Cadillac & Northeastern, Cummer Lumber Co. (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 and train at depot, Cadillac, Mich., [LR138] (Box 1)
    - Mitchell Bros., Jennings, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Shay engine and log train, [LR139] (Box 1)
    - Murphy & Diggins, Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Shay engine 6 and log train, [LR140] (Box 1)
    - Dunham & Peters, Chase, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Shay engine and train, [LR141] (Box 1)
    - Cummer Lumber Co., Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine and log train, [LR142] (Box 1)
    - Logs in lake at Cadillac, Mich., [LR143] (Box 1)
    - Narrow gauge track through woods near Cadillac, Mich., [LR144] (Box 1)
    - E. Shay, Haring, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Supposed to be Shay experimental 1870s, [LR145] (Box 1)
    - Robbins Lumber Co., Eagle River, Wis. (Box 1)
    - Engine 6 and log train, Columbus Lake, Wis. 1908, [LR146] (Box 1)
    - Hemlock Central, E. Shay & Sons, Harbor Springs, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, [LR147] (Box 1)
    - Cody & Moore, Lake City, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 22 and log train on side of Clam River near Falmouth, Mich. 1885, [LR148] (Box 1)
    - Hovey & McCracken, Lake City, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 2, [LR149] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 near Moorestown, Mich. circa 1897, [LR150] (Box 1)
    - Hemlock Central, E. Shay & Son, Harbor Springs, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, earliest known photo, [LR151] (Box 1)
    - Cutler & Savidge Lumber Co., Edmore, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine D. Cutler, advertising cut, [LR152] (Box 1)
    - Foster Blackman & Co. (Box 1)
    - Engine H.B. Blackman, [LR153] (Box 1)
    - Jennings & Northeastern, Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - Engine 8 and log train crossing Manistee River, Smithville, Kalkaska County, Mich., [LR154] (Box 1)
    - Thayer Lumber Co. (Box 1)
    - Dumping logs into West Branch of Muskegon River at the Rollway near Merritt circa 1890, [LR155] (Box 1)
    - Engine 97 and log train, [LR156-158] (Box 1)
    - Jennings & Northeastern, Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - McGiffert log loader, [LR159] (Box 1)
    - Hall & Manning, Deer Lake, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Old Shay engine 1885, [LR160] (Box 1)
    - Kreetan Co., Drummond Island, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Two engines circa 1915, [LR161] (Box 1)
    - Covell Brothers, Hesperia, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine in camp, [LR162] (Box 1)
    - Higbee & Hugh, Morley, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine and log train, [LR163] (Box 1)
    - Lake George & Muskegon River (Box 1)
    - Log train on trestle circa 1880, [LR164] (Box 1)
    - Wm. Crippen & Son, Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Advertising cut of engine 1885, [LR165] (Box 1)
    - E. Shay, Haring, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Patent plate, [LR166] (Box 1)
    - Staples & Covell (Box 1)
    - Engine and log train, [LR167] (Box 1)
    - Wreck east of New Era, Mich. 1894, [LR168] (Box 1)
    - Detail of LR168, [LR168a] (Box 1)
    - Cummer & Diggins, Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, [LR169] (Box 1)
    - Cummer Lumber Co., Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 5 and log train, [LR170] (Box 1)
    - Steam loader east of Wolverine, Mich., at Shurer camp, [LR171] (Box 1)
    - T.L. Hackney, Corrigan, Texas (Box 1)
    - Shay engine, [LR172] (Box 1)
    - Lake Superior Iron & Chemical Co. (Box 1)
    - Engine 10, [LR173] (Box 1)
    - Portage Lake & Muskegon River, Blodgett & Byrnes, Grayling, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine D.A. Blodgett, [LR174] (Box 1)
    - Spring Harbor Railroad, Wm. T. Addis & Co., Bay Springs, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine META, [LR175] (Box 1)
    - Henry Stephens & Co., St. Helen, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 and log train, [LR176] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 and log train at rollway, [LR177] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 and log train near Chase, Mich., [LR178] (Box 1)
    - Cummer Lumber Co., Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine and log train, [LR179] (Box 1)
    - Hauling logs on pole road with teams near Chase, Mich., [LR180] (Box 1)
    - Seaman & Webster, Chase, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine, [LR181] (Box 1)
    - Engine at mill, [LR182] (Box 1)
    - Thayer Lumber Co., Stratford, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 9 and log train, [LR183] (Box 1)
    - Jennings & Northeastern, Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - Engine 9 and log train crossing bridge, Smithville, Mich., [LR184] (Box 1)
    - Beaver Island Lumber Co., Beaver Island, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Pere Marquette engine C at mill circa 1910, [LR185] (Box 1)
    - Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - Shay engine at Hovey & McCracken camp near Stratford, Mich. circa 1898, [LR186] (Box 1)
    - Lake George & Muskegon River(?) (Box 1)
    - Porter engine, [LR187] (Box 1)
    - Sanger Lumber Co., Sanger, Calif. (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 and lumber train, [LR188] (Box 1)
    - E. Shay, Haring, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Patent 242992, [LR189-191] (Box 1)
    - W. Crippen, Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Patent 266103, [LR192-193] (Box 1)
    - Jennings & Northeastern, Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - Log train, Hopkins Valley near Jennings, Mich., [LR194] (Box 1)
    - E. Shay & Son, Hemlock Central, Harbor Springs, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine Baby in woods, [LR195] (Box 1)
    - Engine Baby and car, [LR196] (Box 1)
    - E. Shay running Engine Baby, [LR197] (Box 1)
    - Tearing up track circa 1912, [LR198-200] (Box 1)
    - West Michigan Lumber Co. (Box 1)
    - Engine 2, Woodville, Mich., [LR201] (Box 1)
    - Horning & Hart, Keno, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine and log train, [LR202] (Box 1)
    - Buckley & Douglas, Manistee, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, [LR203] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 at engine house, [LR204] (Box 1)
    - Engines 1 and 2 on flat cars, [LR205] (Box 1)
    - Foster Blackman & Co., Baldwin, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 60 and log train, [LR206] (Box 1)
    - Jennings & Northeastern, Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - Engine 8, Jennings, Mich., [LR207] (Box 1)
    - Engine 12, Jennings, Mich., [LR208] (Box 1)
    - Crawford & Manistee River (Box 1)
    - Engine Nicolas, [LR209] (Box 1)
    - J. Alley & Co., Alleyton, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engines 1 and 2, [LR210] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 and train at rollway, White River, Mich. circa 1880, [LR211] (Box 1)
    - D.N. McLeod, Newberry, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Phoenix steam hauler 1901, [LR212] (Box 1)
    - Henry Stephens & Co., St. Helen, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Porter engine, [LR213] (Box 1)
    - Moore, Park & Sharpe (Box 1)
    - Steam hauler, Shelldrake, Mich. 1907, [LR214-215] (Box 1)
    - Wilson, Luther & Wilson, Luther, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Shay and Heisler engines, [LR216] (Box 1)
    - Engine 6, [LR217] (Box 1)
    - Bear Lake & Eastern, Hopkins Manufacturing Co., Bear Lake, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 on trestle, [LR218] (Box 1)
    - Shay engine and cars at Pierport, [LR219] (Box 1)
    - Hobart & Manistee River, Canfield Road (Box 1)
    - Camp at River terminus circa 1880, [LR220] (Box 1)
    - Log train on trestle circa 1880, [LR221-222] (Box 1)
    - Wm. Crippen & Son, Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Crippen locomotive advertising card 1882, [LR223] (Box 1)
    - Description of Crippen locomotive, back of advertising card 1882, [LR224] (Box 1)
    - Cobbs & Mitchell, Cadillac, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and log train, [LR225] (Box 1)
    - J.H. Worden, Cedar Springs, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Mill and crew circa 1898, [LR226] (Box 1)
    - Engine and crew circa 1898, [LR227-228] (Box 1)
    - Chippewa Lumber Co., Chippewa Lake, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine and log train, [LR229] (Box 1)
    - Two engines and log train, [LR230] (Box 1)
    - Jennings & Northeastern, Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - Log train near Spencer, Mich., [LR231] (Box 1)
    - Engine 6 on trestle, Jennings, Mich., [LR232] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7, [LR233-234] (Box 1)
    - Engine 10 and log train, Spencer, Mich., [LR235] (Box 1)
    - Engine 10, [LR236] (Box 1)
    - Early Shay engine unidentified, [LR237] (Box 1)
    - Cadillac & Northeastern, Cummer Lumber Co. (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 and first train, Lake City, Mich., [LR238] (Box 1)
    - Crescent & Southeastern, A.J. White, North Manitou Island, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and log train 1909, [LR239] (Box 1)
    - Paris & Pere Marquette River, Palmer Nichols & Co. (Box 1)
    - Three engines in front of engine house, [LR240] (Box 1)
    - Loading logs in woods, [LR241] (Box 1)
    - New York Lumber Co. (Box 1)
    - Camp near Pinchtown, Newaygo County, Mich. 1880s, [LR242] (Box 1)
    - Blaney & Southern, Wisconsin Land & Lumber Co. (Box 1)
    - Cadillac auto converted for rail service, [LR243] (Box 1)
    - Hoerner Waldorf Corp., Ontonagon, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 6 on display 1969, [LR244] (Box 1)
    - Jennings & Northeastern, Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - Engine 10, [LR245] (Box 1)
    - E. Shay & Son, Hemlock Central, Harbor Springs, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 in woods 1905, [LR246] (Box 1)
    - Lobdell & Bailey Manufacturing Co., Onaway, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Shay engine and log train, [LR247] (Box 1)
    - Engine and log train, [LR248] (Box 1)
    - Engine and log train on trestle, [LR249] (Box 1)
    - West Michigan Lumber Co., Woodville, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Log train crossing C&WM tracks at Woodville, [LR250] (Box 1)
    - Jennings & Northeastern, Mitchell Bros. (Box 1)
    - Engine 7 and log train, [LR251] (Box 1)
    - Engine 14, [LR252] (Box 1)
    - Staples & Covell, New Era, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Two engines in woods, [LR253] (Box 1)
    - Nessen Lumber Co., Glen Arbor, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Porter engine, [LR254] (Box 1)
    - Dwight Lumber Co., Blanchard, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Two engines at water tank, [LR255] (Box 1)
    - Staples & Covell, New Era, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Two engines at engine houses, [LR256] (Box 1)
    - Porter engine and train at rollway on White River, [LR257] (Box 1)
    - Thayer Lumber Co., Stratford, Mich. (Box 1)
    - Engine 97, [LR258] (Box 1)
  - Lake Superior & Ishpeming
    (Code LSI)
    - Snow Plow, Munising, Mich. 1951, [LSI1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 29, Negaunee, Mich. 1952, [LSI2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3, [LSI3-4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, [LSI5] (Box 1)
    - Engines 20 and 21 on scrap track, Marquette, Mich. 1969, [LSI6] (Box 1)
    - Engines 18 and 22 on scrap track, Marquette, Mich. 1969, [LSI7] (Box 1)
    - Engines 19 and 34 on scrap track, Marquette, Mich. 1969, [LSI8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 29 on scrap track, Marquette, Mich. 1969, [LSI9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 35 on scrap track, Marquette, Mich. 1969, [LSI10] (Box 1)
    - Marquette & Huron Mountain Engine 23 on scrap track, Marquette, Mich. 1969, [LSI11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 24, National Railroad Museum, Green Bay, Wis. 1970, [LSI12] (Box 1)
  - Lake Shore & Michigan Southern
    (Code SLIMS)
    - Engine 1, Henry Ford Museum 1937, [LSMS1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 689, [LSMS2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 826, [LSMS3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 67 and train, Ypsilanti, Mich. circa 1900, [LSMS4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 338, [LSMS5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 262, [LSMS6-8] (Box 1)
    - New York Central Lines Engine 4194 and passenger train, [LSMS9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 71, [LSMS10] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4695, [LSMS11] (Box 1)
    - Station, Hanover, Mich. circa 1900, [LSMS12] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5045 circa 1910, [LSMS13] (Box 1)
    - Centennial business card 1876, [LSMS14] (Box 1)
    - Engine 136, [LSMS15] (Box 1)
    - Engine 485, [LSMS16] (Box 1)
    - Engine 695, [LSMS17] (Box 1)
    - Fort Wayne, Jackson & Saginaw Engine Ft. Wayne 1870, [LSMS18] (Box 1)
    - Michigan & Ohio Engine 1, [LSMS19] (Box 1)
    - Engine 51, [LSMS20] (Box 1)
    - Engine 242, [LSMS21] (Box 1)
    - Station, Tecumseh, Mich. 1885, [LSMS22] (Box 1)
    - Detail of LSMS22, [LSMS22a] (Box 1)
    - Head-on collision east of Tecumseh, Engine 5114 and DT&I Engine 77 1907, [LSMS23] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4758 and passenger train, Clinton, Mich., [LSMS24] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4759 and passenger train, Clinton, Mich., [LSMS25] (Box 1)
    - Engine 67 and passenger train on bridge, Manchester, Mich., [LSMS26] (Box 1)
    - Engine 240, Detroit, Mich., [LSMS27] (Box 1)
    - Engine 167, Norvell, Mich., [LSMS28] (Box 1)
    - Engine 67, Brooklyn, Mich. circa 1890, [LSMS29] (Box 1)
    - Advertising cut of Michigan Southern Steamer Northern Indiana, [LSMS30] (Box 1)
    - Engine 604 and passenger train, [LSMS31] (Box 1)
    - Engine 72, Adrian, Mich. 1867, [LSMS32] (Box 1)
    - Erie & Kalamazoo bank note 1853, [LSMS33] (Box 1)
    - Erie & Kalamazoo Engine 1 (wood cut), [LSMS34] (Box 1)
    - Engine 95 circa 1900, [LSMS35] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4565 and passenger train, Hudson, Mich., [LSMS36] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5013 and passenger train, Hudson, Mich. circa 1910, [LSMS37] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train, Hudson, Mich., [LSMS38] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train on bridge, Jerome, Mich. circa 1915, [LSMS39] (Box 1)
  - Michigan Railway
    (Code M)
    - Car 513, Jackson, Mich., [M1] (Box 1)
    - Car 516, Jackson, Mich., [M2] (Box 1)
    - Car 548, Jackson, Mich., [M3] (Box 1)
    - Car 552, Jackson, Mich., [M4] (Box 1)
    - Car 553, Jackson, Mich., [M5] (Box 1)
    - Car 559, Jackson, Mich., [M6] (Box 1)
    - Car 82, Battle Creek, Mich., [M7] (Box 1)
    - Car 700, Owosso, Mich., [M8] (Box 1)
    - Car 348 (sweeper), Kalamazoo, Mich., [M9] (Box 1)
    - Car 303, Kalamazoo, Mich., [M10] (Box 1)
    - Car 329, Kalamazoo, Mich., [M11] (Box 1)
    - Car 346, Kalamazoo, Mich., [M12] (Box 1)
    - Car 352, Kalamazoo, Mich., [M13] (Box 1)
    - Car 417, Battle Creek, Mich., [M14] (Box 1)
    - Car 658, [M15] (Box 1)
    - Car 44, [M16] (Box 1)
    - Car 45, [M17] (Box 1)
    - Car 48, [M18] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Parma, Mich., [M19] (Box 1)
    - Main St. with car, Parma, Mich., [M20] (Box 1)
    - Wreck of Car 7522 Parma, Mich. 1923, [M21] (Box 1)
  - Manistique Railway
    (Code Man)
    - Engine 3 1894, [Man1] (Box 1)
  - Maps
    (Code Map)
    - Lower Peninsula, Mich., from Wood's Railway Guide December 1889, [Map1-3] (Box 1)
  - Michigan Central
    (Code MC)
    - Engine 509 and passenger train, Dexter, Mich. circa 1900, [MC1] (Box 1)
    - Bridge between Ann Arbor and Dexter, Mich. circa 1890, [MC2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 245, Delhi, Mich. 1889, [MC3] (Box 1)
    - North Shore Limited on bridge between Ann Arbor and Dexter, Mich. circa 1890, [MC4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 245 and freight train on bridge near Delhi, Mich. 1889, [MC5] (Box 1)
    - Mallet used in hump yard, Junction Yard, Detroit, Mich. 1917, [MC6] (Box 1)
    - Engine 60, Kalamazoo, Mich. 1888, [MC7a] (Box 1)
    - Engine 60, Kalamazoo, Mich. 1888 wrecked, [MC7b] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8000 and Engine 8977 Detroit, Mich. 1922, [MC8] (Box 1)
    - Station, North Lansing, Mich., MC and DL&N circa 1900, [MC9] (Box 1)
    - Station, Ypsilanti, Mich. 1865, [MC10] (Box 1)
    - Yards, Ypsilanti, Mich. 1870s, [MC11] (Box 1)
    - Flower gardens, Ypsilanti, Mich. 1893, [MC12] (Box 1)
    - Engine 201, Ypsilanti, Mich., late 1880s, [MC13] (Box 1)
    - Oshtemo Diversion, work train with dump cars 1903-1904, [MC14] (Box 1)
    - Oshtemo Diversion, work train with steam shovel 1903-1904, [MC15] (Box 1)
    - Oshtemo Diversion, Engine 26 and work train at dump 1903-1904, [MC16] (Box 1)
    - Oshtemo Diversion, work train at Miller Fill 1903-1904, [MC17] (Box 1)
    - Engine 165, Grayling, Mich. 1870s, [MC18] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8456 and passenger train, Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1910, [MC19] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7958 and passenger train east of Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1910, [MC20] (Box 1)
    - Yards with snowplow and Engine 8204 Wolverine, Mich. 1910, [MC21] (Box 1)
    - Engine 639, Gaylord, Mich. 1900, [MC22] (Box 1)
    - Engine 124, [MC23] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8936 and passenger train at station, Lewiston, Mich. circa 1912, [MC24] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8243 at station, Eaton Rapids, Mich. circa 1910, [MC25] (Box 1)
    - Collision, Chelsea, Mich. 1887, [MC26] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7972 derailed, Otter Lake, Mich. circa 1915, [MC27] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train, Otter Lake, Mich. circa 1915, [MC28] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train taking water, Kinnear track pan east of Dexter, Mich. circa 1907, [MC29] (Box 1)
    - Employee time card, [MC30-31] (Box 1)
    - Bucking snow, Gaylord, Mich. 1913, [MC32] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7710 and caboose, [MC33] (Box 1)
    - Engine 27, [MC34] (Box 1)
    - Engine 191 and passenger train circa 1880, [MC35] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8363, [MC36] (Box 1)
    - Engine 115, [MC37] (Box 1)
    - Engine 15, [MC38] (Box 1)
    - Work train on bridge, Ypsilanti, Mich. circa 1870s, [MC39] (Box 1)
    - Engine 47, first engine into South Haven, Mich. 1871, [MC40] (Box 1)
    - Engine 86, Ypsilanti, Mich. 1860s, [MC41] (Box 1)
    - Engine 164, [MC42] (Box 1)
    - Engine 20, [MC43] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Parma, Mich., [MC44-45] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Grass Lake, Mich., [MC46] (Box 1)
    - Wreck, Grass Lake, Mich. 1902, [MC47-48] (Box 1)
    - Yard, Grayling, Mich. circa 1910, [MC49] (Box 1)
    - Wreck of Engine 496, Lewiston, Mich., branch circa 1905, [MC50-51] (Box 1)
    - Wreck of Engine 8981, Kibbie, Mich. 1908, [MC52] (Box 1)
    - Engine 188 and passenger train, Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1890, [MC53] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8362, [MC54] (Box 1)
    - Station, Charlotte, Mich., [MC55] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Ann Arbor, Mich., middle 1880s, [MC56] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train leaving Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1912, [MC57] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Chelsea, Mich. circa 1915, [MC58] (Box 1)
    - Canada Southern Engine 337, Comber, Ont. circa 1890, [MC59] (Box 1)
    - Engine 49, [MC60] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Spring Arbor, Mich., [MC61] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Cheboygan, Mich., [MC62] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Topinabee, Mich., [MC63] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8203 and freight train, Mason, Mich. circa 1910, [MC64] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Standish, Mich., [MC65] (Box 1)
    - Wreck of Engine 7720 near Grayling, Mich. 1910, [MC66] (Box 1)
    - Wreck south of Grayling, Mich. circa 1910, [MC67] (Box 1)
  - Michigan Electric Railway
    (Code MER)
    - Wreck at corner of Huron and Main, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1928, [MER1-7] (Box 1)
  - Manistee & Grand Rapids
    (Code MGR)
    - Wreck of cattle train near Filer City, Mich., [MGR1] (Box 1)
    - Washout 1913, [MGR2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2 and log train near Filer City, Mich., [MGR3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8, [MGR4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, Dighton, Mich. 1918, [MGR5] (Box 1)
    - Sand loader, Manistee, Mich., [MGR6] (Box 1)
    - Wreck of freight train near Filer City, Mich., [MGR7-8] (Box 1)
    - Engine stuck in snow near Filer City, Mich. circa 1900, [MGR9] (Box 1)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul & Pacific
    (Milwaukee Road)
    (Code Milw)
    - Engine 319, Escanaba, Mich. 1951, [Milw1] (Box 1)
  - McKeen Motor Car Co.
    (Code MK)
    - Motor car supposed to be Ann Arbor car 1912, [MK1] (Box 1)
    - Six motor cars in transit 1912, [MK2] (Box 1)
    - Power truck 1912, [MK3-4] (Box 1)
    - Letterhead 1920, [MK5] (Box 1)
  - Manistee & Luther
    (Code ML)
    - R.G. Peters mill, Eastlake, Mich. 1894, [ML1-2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2, [ML3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5, [ML4] (Box 1)
    - Wooden trestle on R.G. Peters logging road, [ML5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3, [ML6] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7, [ML7] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2, [ML8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5 and log train, [ML9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 6 and log train on trestle, [ML10] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, [ML11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5, [ML12] (Box 1)
    - Engines 1 and 5 on log train, late 1890s, [ML13] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and log train on South Branch bridge circa 1900, [ML14] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, [ML15] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, Hoxeyville, Mich., yard, [ML16] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2, [ML17] (Box 1)
    - Colorado & Southern Engine 34 and log train on M&L circa 1901, [ML18] (Box 1)
    - Engines 4 and 5 in yard, Hoxeyville, Mich., [ML19] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5 circa 1905, [ML20] (Box 1)
    - Engine 6 and log train, [ML21] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7 1908, [ML22] (Box 1)
    - Skidder crew loading car circa 1909, [ML23] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7 1880s, [ML24] (Box 1)
  - Manistique & Lake Superior
    (Code MLS)
    - Engine 2140 Manistique, Mich. 1941, [MLS1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2140 Manistique, Mich. 1941, [MLS2] (Box 1)
    - Combination coach and baggage car, Manistique, Mich. 1941, [MLS3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2370 Manistique, Mich. 1953, [MLS4-5] (Box 1)
    - Scrapping engines 2370 and 2390 Owosso, Mich. 1953, [MLS6-10] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2370 Manistique, Mich., [MLS11] (Box 1)
  - Manistique, Marquette & Northern
    (Code MMN)
    - Carferry no. 1, Frankfort, Mich., [MMN1-2] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 1, Northport, Mich., [MMN3] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 1, [MMN4] (Box 1)
  - Manistee & North Eastern
    (Code MNE)
    - Engine 12 and train, Traverse City, Mich. 1939, [MNE1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and log train circa 1890, [MNE2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 26, [MNE3-4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 27, [MNE5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 325, [MNE6] (Box 1)
    - Engine 9 and coach stuck in snow south of Suttons Bay, Mich., [MNE7] (Box 1)
    - Roundhouse fire, Manistee, Mich. 1936, [MNE8-11] (Box 1)
    - Snow plow no. 3, [MNE12] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Nessen City, Mich., [MNE13] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Traverse City, Mich., [MNE14] (Box 1)
    - Snowplow no. 2, Manistee, Mich. circa 1930, [MNE15] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2 at Buckley & Douglas camp, [MNE16] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8 1937, [MNE17] (Box 1)
    - Engine 474 1937, [MNE18] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8 near Northport, Mich., [MNE19] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2, [MNE20] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and passenger car circa 1900, [MNE21] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 and mixed train circa 1900, [MNE22] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8 and freight train circa 1900, [MNE23] (Box 1)
    - Engine 9 and freight train circa 1900, [MNE24] (Box 1)
    - Engine 10 and passenger train circa 1900, [MNE25] (Box 1)
    - Engine 11 and work train circa 1900, [MNE26] (Box 1)
    - Engine 12 and freight train circa 1900, [MNE27] (Box 1)
    - Engine 14 and passenger train circa 1900, [MNE28] (Box 1)
    - Engine 15 and passenger train circa 1900, [MNE29] (Box 1)
    - Engine 11, early 1900s, [MNE30-31] (Box 1)
    - Engine 18, [MNE32-33] (Box 1)
    - Engine 11 and caboose 9 at depot, Honor, Mich., [MNE34] (Box 1)
    - Station just before demolition, Traverse City, Mich., [MNE35] (Box 1)